<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[One Love Fest ICO]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[One Love Fest ICO]]></description>
        <link>http://onelove.eco/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 13:17:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://onelove.eco/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 13:17:07 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sharing One Love with ALL]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Sharing One Love with ALL</strong></h1>,<p>An experiment in love, celebration, and consciousness like nothing we have ever experienced before.</p>,<p>Imagine an experience where people of goodwill come together to expand, deepen, and share the Love that connects us all, where everyone experiences grace and healing, explorations in a variety of Vibrations of LOVE, and a celebration of themselves and each other. 2018’s ONE LOVE represents an ever evolving living crucible for human heart transformation, celebration and fellowship. The festival will consist of a 4 day interactive mystery school template, where self-transformation meets creative community celebration, collaboration, and expression, facilitated by a new earth template gifted economy exchange.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/28b58f9f-0972-46b0-bbc5-6b92b8b73a9c.jpg">,<p>There are two new Interwoven Pioneering Architectures in this festival experience:</p>,<h2>LOVE-BASED GIFT ECONOMY</h2>,<p>Imagine an event where people of goodwill come together and celebrate beauty, individuality and sharing, where there is no money, where all exchanges are gifting in one or both directions. If you’ve been to the Burning Man festival you know how magical and life-changing such an experience of Love and connection can be.</p>,<p>Now imagine the next step of evolution. Imagine a magical festival with all of the above but created from the ground up completely by gifts of Love, attended by participants who are given access as a gift of Love, where no money is required for food or drink or anything else.</p>,<p>How is such a thing possible? We invite you to participate in an experiment whose time has come.</p>,<h3>I AM/WE ARE ONE LOVE - FESTIVAL QUEST EXPERIENCE</h3>,<p>Imagine a coming to a festival where you are a participant in four days of sacred exploration where the entire festival is intentionally designed as an ceremonial adventure map for transforming and expanding the heart. Patrons will be able map aspects of their soul and select from a variety of quests that allow them to experience self-transformation within themselves, within each Heart Realm of the festival. Questing will invoke experiences in heart-centered self practice, workshops, single, coupled and group activities, with ceremonial musical experiences integrating these teachings into the soul of your heart. The I AM LOVE Quests focuses on bringing into awareness, surrendering, and embodying heart based knowledge, skills and wisdom, for self love and expansion of the heart in practice with others. We Are Quests focus on the collective, and include group based quests, learning to love the larger whole, love based service to the many, and large population attunements of heart based sound resonance.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1cd117f5-59b3-43c7-9e71-3ebf2e2162d9.png">,<h3><strong>Assumptions</strong></h3>,<p>To get there from here, we have to agree on some basics:</p>,<ol><li>(+) Love expresses connection and harmony</li><li>(-) Fear expresses separation and disharmony</li><li>Love is the highest form of value in voluntary interactions</li><li>Goodwill is necessary to experience the maximum results of this experiment. Goodwill is a gift of Love. Ill will is an expression of Fear. Harmony grows from EXCHANGES OF LOVE, by whatever token or action.</li></ol>,<p>If you agree to these assumptions, the rest becomes possible.</p>,<h3><strong>One Love History Sets the Stage</strong></h3>,<p>Over the prior six years everyone in the One Love Festival has co-created something exponentially bigger than the sum of their contributions. For lack of a better name, let’s call it the One Love Ethos. [Brief statement of some of the wonders of this ethos as experienced by participants?] No individual person or group could possibly own this phenomenon. We can only acknowledge that it has a life of its own and nourish it together as ONE, according to the ability and willingness of each. If you’ve gone to other festivals, you’ve likely experienced some of this same energy. But One Love has been very special.</p>,<p>We could do One Love like always and it would still be wonderful. But evolving technologies make more evolution possible. Wouldn’t you LOVE to be part of an experiment designed to set the One Love spirit free in the world to spread virally way beyond just one festival? More Love, less fear?</p>,<h3><strong>Love is a Gift from the Heart, Not the Pocket</strong></h3>,<p>Value is a weird thing. Nobody sees value quite the same. Money is very useful but can really mess with our ideas about what real value is. What is satisfactory in exchange for a kind word? A “Thank you”? At least. A smile? Usually more prized. A hug? Ah, now that’s golden! A dollar? Uh . . . Is “insult” a strong enough term?</p>,<p>You CAN use money to show love. But mainly we think of money as “a necessary evil” tainted by fear and greed. Isn’t it sad that the first thing we think when asked what something is worth is also considered “the root of all evil” and not “a whole lot of love”?</p>,<p>This year’s One Love Festival will be powered <em>exclusively</em> by Love!</p>,<p>No one will be able to buy a ticket! But the Festival will be packed!</p>,<p>Money won’t buy a meal there! But everyone will have plenty!</p>,<p>How can that be?? Ah, you’ll see.</p>,<p>For now, practice seeing the fear that separates, and experience the Love that connects. After all, that’s the change you really want to see in the world, right?</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://onelove.eco/sharing-one-love-with-all/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e3e74bd3-0a51-4a84-861a-7ac66f0a240d</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 09:20:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One Love Content Co-Creation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>One Love Content Co-Creation</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3e7030e0-90b8-493d-b335-5d8185eced89.jpg">,<h2>This page will for now serve as the place for our collective works of co-creation of One Love.</h2>,<h3>Podcasts</h3>,<article><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4fa966bfc4247e37fa63cbb988344e3c039df76a.jpg"><h1>Lets Talk Bitcoin: Technology &amp; Choice #26, Reconnection - Ken Schwenker and the One Love Festival - Steemit</h1><p>Thank you John Ferguson for all you are doing to help our One Love Fest November 2-4th 2018 being the first full... by onelove-eco</p></article>,<article><img src="https://steemitimages.com/DQmQTPFdktAmJwWJq8LPgFfdR76qusG1LxLd7RYpcahYTAL/377A4344.jpg"><h1>Let&apos;s Talk Bitcoin - Technology &amp; Choice #27, Lucien Vattel on the I AM Tech Stack - Steemit</h1><p>&quot;I Am&quot; is a technology stack that is evolving to incorporate high tech, to aide a process of personal and social improvement and connection. Our guest, Lucien Vattel, has years of experience in developing technologies to assist in learning and general education.</p></article>,<h3>Articles &amp; Blogs</h3>,<h3>Marketing Material</h3>]]></description>
            <link>http://onelove.eco/one-love-content-co-creation/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">38a3b90f-4e3e-4e68-8ed3-e9ce075404e9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 23:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proof of Fan]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Proof of Fan</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8bf8dde1-bdca-4006-acb9-1a16a0766a12.jpg">,<p>This is where an active list of performers, musicians, artists, and spiritual leaders who have received votes from the <a href="https://t.me/onelovefestival" title="Click to join our telegram group">telegram group, One Love Fest</a>, to attend the 2018 One Love Fest in Lake Perris, Califonia November 2-4th. We are developing a voting bot that will welcome new users to the group and show them how to vote right in the telegram group on who they want to see at the 2018 One Love Fest.</p>,<p>This helps the organizers of the festival focus their resources towards building a relationship with the most desired creatives and their fans. Plus it will allow fans to build up demand and a community to support these inspiring people within the One Love Eco.</p>,<h2>Current Proof-of-Fan Board (February 6th)</h2>,<ol><li><a href="https://thepolishambassador.com/" title="Official Artist site">Polish Ambassador</a></li><li><a href="https://dirtwire.net/" title="Click to view Dirtwire's site">Dirtwire</a></li><li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/djmija/" title="Facebook Page">Mija</a></li><li><a href="http://www.aboveandbeyond.nu/" title="Go to Above &amp; Beyond's site">Above &amp; Beyond</a></li><li><a href="http://www.kaskademusic.com/" title="Click to view Kaskade's site">Kaskade</a></li><li><a href="http://www.bigwildmusic.com/" title="Click to view Big Wild">Big Wild</a></li><li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/TaleOfUs/" title="Click to view their facebook">Tale Of Us</a></li><li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/MaceoPlex/" title="Click to view their facebook page">Maceo Plex</a></li><li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/tempimusic" title="Click to view TEMPI facebook">TEMPI</a></li><li><a href="http://www.outersect.net/" title="Official Site">Outersect</a></li><li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL6khfg3nGvffG7Pm5T-bFTxND_zIbKCDS&amp;feature=gws_kp_artist&amp;app=desktop" title="Collection of Tracks">Scott Nice</a></li><li><a href="https://soundcloud.com/friend_music/catharsis311" title="Collection of Music">Friend</a></li><li><a href="https://soundcloud.com/madamegandhi/sets/voices" title="posted by fan">Madame Gandhi</a></li><li><a href="https://soundcloud.com/grouchnz/grouch-soul-provider-full" title="posted by telegram group fan">Grouch in Dub</a></li><li><a href="https://frameworksuk.bandcamp.com/" title="Official Artist Site">Frameworks</a></li><li><a href="https://soundcloud.com/troyboi" title="Click to listen to artist music">TroyBoi</a></li></ol>,<a href="https://t.me/onelovefestival" data-role="cta">Join One Love Fest Telegram</a>]]></description>
            <link>http://onelove.eco/proof-of-fan/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ae8d2074-ee80-4e50-975a-32d1b4f0e340</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 18:49:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Network & Community Partners]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Network &amp; Community Partners</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9354e258-ce3b-4f49-ac49-14b851057d91.jpg">,<p><strong><a href="https://eos.io/" title="EOS by block.one">EOS by block.one</a></strong> - The Most Powerful Infrastructure for Decentralized Applications. Support thousands of Commercial Scale DApps. Freeze and Fix Broken Applications. Web Toolkit for Interface Development, Self Describing Interfaces, Self Describing Database Schemes and Declarative Permission Scheme.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://onelove.eco/network-and-community-partners/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c8e5103d-81ab-46d7-b1e0-30ab510e10b4</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 20:16:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>